http://www.steffensdinners.com/content/steffens_dinners_privacy_policy

Steffen's Dinners - Recipes and PhotosSimple - Elegant - Beautiful
Apple Pancakes
Braised Oxtail (Pressure Cooker)
Weiﬂwurst ("White Sausage")
Filet Mignon with Asparagus on Espuma of Chanterelles
K‰sekuchen (German Cheesecake)
Home ª Steffen's Dinners Privacy Policy Steffen's Dinners Privacy Policy
Fri, 08/01/2008 - 20:57 ó admin
Printer-friendly versionPDF versionPrivacy Policy
Here you will find information about what kinds of information may be collected when you visit this site.
Visitor-contributed Comments
You may leave comments on this site. When you do so, you can optionally provide an e-mail address and a web site URL. We will never publish, sell or otherwise provide your e-mail address to anyone. If you choose to provide a web site URL, it will be linked from your comment.
Log Files
As most other websites, www.steffensdinners.com collects and uses data in log files. The information includes your IP (internet protocol) address, date and time of your visit, the referring site, the browser (such as Firefox or Internet Explorer) and operating system
(identified by the
HTTP_USER_AGENT header) you used to visit this site, and a record of all
the pages you visit on www.steffensdinners.com.
We use the excellent awstats package to automatically analyze the logfiles.
Cookies and Web Beacons
www.steffensdinners.com may use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit the site.
Third Party Advertisers
We use third party advertisements (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) to support the site. We may also show other third party widgets. These third parties may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise or display a widget on this site, which will also send them
information including your IP address, your Internet Service Provider (ISP), the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash or other plugins installed. This information is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
Web Analytics
In addition to our local analytics software (Piwik) we are also using third party analytics tools (such as Google Analytics). All the analytics tools, local and third party, may use JavaScript and cookies to capture additional information about your visit, your browser and your computer, such as screen resolution, installed plugins and
time on the site.
Reducing the Amount of Data Collected / Opt Out
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. You can also turn off JavaScript in your browser. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.
This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Please note that even if you disable cookies and JavaScript, visit information as described above under Log Files will still be recorded.
Data Retention and Privacy
Log files are kept up to 16 weeks for auditing purposes. Local analytics data is aggregated and anonymized at regular intervals, typically a day. None of this information will be sold or disclosed to third parties. For all data collected by third parties, their respective privacy and data retention policies apply.
Acknowledgements
Thanks to JenSense for an initial template for this Privacy Policy.
Printer-friendly version
PDF version
Search
RSS 2.0 Feed
Except for guest comments and ads, all original content of this site is © S. Luitz 2007-2015, www-admin AT steffensdinners.com
See the privacy policy for information about what we or third parties may record about your visit
All original content of this site is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-No Derivative Works 3.0 United States License. Attribution for photos should be provided by linking back to this site or the specific recipe page or by referencing this site.
Log In
Beta Site
